I'm pretty sure this probably exists in
some paid format online but a body slash
health website that go that you like
it's two human bodies in the two main
when there's some differences that
anyway
the two main body types usually
characterized as male female and being
able to zoom in to all the different
organs all the different cells all the
different systems and see how they work
and ways to improve them if you have
problems diseases that can affect them
in a very visual way I would like to
have access to that especially with my
conditions knowing exactly which parts
of my brain I've been cut out post and
you can have even your own profile where
you are actually looking at I mean it's
not your actual body but saying okay
well and animations
I love medical animations and like this
is what happens when we when you're you
know during conception through birth
here's what happens during a bypass
surgery we're not showing the actual
surgery but they're showing you know the
cartoon kind of but really good cartoon
animation that's organismic - yeah so a
online free body website